overnight. We're in a We're in a lull
right now. We're on generator power, so
forgive me if I drop out. Um furniture
everywhere.
>> Wow.
>> And I know it's probably silly, but
when it rains heavily, that's when all
the tarantulas come out of their holes.
[laughter]
>> That's not
>> I have that to greet me. Uh today,
>> do they come inside looking for shelter?
>> The last couple of days, there was one
in the dining room last night.
>> No. And you guys and you have a bunch of
liberals there. So you shoe them out
rather than
>> I there was a moth in my room the size
of a sparrow. Not even a sparrow, a
robin. It was like this bigger than a
sparrow. And and I killed it and it got
that powder everywhere. You know how
monks are.
>> Yeah.
>> And everybody jumped on me that it's one
of God's creatures and I should have
captured it and taken it outside. I
said, I've killed two of them in my room
already. [laughter]
Not to talk not to even talk about the
the family of mice that's in my dresser.
That's why I'm still using suitcases
back here.
>> Yeah. You don't really you can't really
clobber them because they make such a
mess.
>> Not if that's even assuming you can
catch them. They're they're like grease
lightning. They're they're crazy.
>> Yeah.
>> The tarantula situation sounds I have to
say. At least is it is it is the rain
knocking the mosquitoes out of the sky?
Yeah, for the very first time, the rain
is helping with the mosquitoes. Ted, it
is so oppressively
hot and humid here. I feel like I'm
melting. And everybody keeps saying,
"Oh, it's very unusual. This is this is
the weather for for early September, not
early October. It is just stifling."
>> I'm so sorry, John. I mean, I hate
>> having fun the movie.
>> The the star arrived a couple days ago.
Um,
>> are you at liberty to say who the star
is?
>> Yeah, it's Jeff Fehee. He was in
Motorcycle Man and Lost and a whole
bunch of stuff.
>> Oh, what was he? I I was a big fan of
Lost. Do you remember?
>> Oh, yeah. HE WAS HELICOPTER PILOT.
>> OH, THAT GUY'S GREAT.
>> YEAH, he's great.
>> Fantastic. I can't wait to see it. Oh,
that's so cool. Yeah, I've I've never
acted before and it's hard and it's
intimidating, but all these people are
professional actors and so that's what
has made it so much easier
>> for you.
>> Very helpful. I'm enjoying myself very
much.
>> Are they Are they giving you hints and
anything?
>> Yeah.
>> Wow, that's awesome. I love that.
>> It's when I got into When I got into
talk radio, uh Mike Gallagher, the
conservative talk.
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah, sure. He basically
taught me everything I know about talk
radio and uh it was I don't people
others will judge whether that was uh
worth knowing or not. I'm going to go
through a rundown and then we'll bring
in Robbie in for a little business. Um
and then uh we'll get to it. So uh it's
the third ann it's the sorry the second
anniversary of the October 7th Hamas
attack. Um as I put into the thumbnail
Hamas I think we've talked about this
and I hope I think we probably agree on
the idea. Hamas appears to have won. Uh
we'll talk about the future of the
conflict as it enters its third its
third year. Uh Gazlain Max Maxwell's
appeal um to the US Supreme Court was
denied. U we'll talk about whether Trump
plans to pardon her or give her clemency
or whatnot. Um
also uh we've got uh the the the
political crisis in France is deepening
unsurprisingly after uh Sebastian Lu
stepped down. Uh the the stock markets
there labels is uh just completely
roing. The French economy is uh kind of
on the ropes and uh even his first prime
minister is urging uh President Emanuel
Macron to resign. And I think we're
going to see more calls for his
resignation in the coming hours and
days. Um the government shutdown
continues a pace. John, uh you might be
better off not flying around the United
States even there. Uh just uh I was
laughing because and in horror at the
fact that a pilot at Burbank airport
north of LA called the control tower to
get instructions from ATC and basically
got
>> like no one's here to help you due to
short staffing and the government
shutdown. I mean he did manage to get
off the ground I guess with instructions
from LAX but still that's pretty crazy.
So, um, we also should bring in Robbie.
We had a little bit of disconcerting,
uh, financial news that, um, we're gonna
bring you up to speed on. And thanks
everyone for watching us here. We really
appreciate you,
>> Robbie.
>> So, good morning. It seems like every
time that the producer comes on, it's
always bad news.
>> That's not true.
>> And I know Okay, that's not true. But I
do want to kind of rub your nose into
this, John. Uh here in Mont here in here
in Montana, it is currently a steamy 24
degrees
>> and we got frost everywhere. So while
you're there sweltering in Mexico, I
just want to let you know I am very much
enjoying the fact we actually have
seasons here in Montana. So there is
that. But no, let's just uh go into the
news. So first and foremost, YouTube has
demonetized us. Yes, y'all heard that
right. So, for those of you who watch us
on YouTube, uh we appreciate it, but I
just want y'all to know that YouTube
thanks you very much because they are
directly benefiting from your watching,
but John and Ted are not getting a dime
from what y'all are doing. Uh we have uh
we've launched an appeal. There's some
things we're going to try to do, try and
get the situation rectified. Is that
going to happen or not? Listen, I don't
know. YouTube is a part of the beast.
It's a part of the machine. It is what
it is.
Um,
I was worried this was probably going to
happen and here we are. So, if y'all
want to support John and Ted, and I
encourage y'all to do that because for
the show to continue, they've got to
earn money. I mean, they got bills to
pay. Let's just be honest. That's that's
how our society works. If you want to
support the show,
please please please watch us over on
Rumble. And I know that the morning time
that the morning show is inconvenient
for some people. So going forward
starting today, I'm going to start
streaming the exact the morning show at
the old time 5 Eastern 5:00 p. p.m.
Eastern
uh 300 p.m. Mountain time for the see
people in in civilized America where I
am. So y'all going to be able to have
have the morning and the afternoon show.
If you want to support the show on
Rumble, uh you can uh you can of course
donate. You become channel subscribers.
Cost you $5 a month. If you do that,
then you get to see the premium eps
they're going to be dropping with John
and Ted. John's entire story is up. Ted
started yesterday.
And uh basically that's really all I've
got. If y'all want if y'all want the
program to survive, we need your help.
And right now Rumble is the one that's
throwing us to Lifeline. Watch us on
Rumble. They pay us off of watch hours.
you can donate, become channel
subscribers
because I mean
me being the good capitalist that I am
and the right-wing capitalist at that, I
don't like the idea of working for
someone for free.
>> And that's what we're doing right now on
YouTube.
>> And if if I know there are a lot of
people who don't like this option, but
this and for you,
>> PayPal is an option, too.
>> PayPal is an option. Here's the PayPal
address. DProgrampodcast@gmail.com.
It's dprogrampodcast@gmail.com.
Okay, Robbie, thank you so much for
that.
>> And uh and big shout out to Scott over
there on Rumble. Uh thank you for what
you do. [__] YouTube. And I
wholeheartedly agree with that message.
[__] you, YouTube. [laughter]
>> All right, Robbie, we'll see you later.
All right, let's get to it. Um what do
you want to talk about first? You want
to talk about France shutdown Jizlain or
uh or Gaza?
And actually, if you don't mind, I'd
like to talk about France because I have
a a question. I think probably a lot of
people have this question.
>> Um, in in my memory, you know, going
back to
George Pompedu or maybe, you know, maybe
even before, I don't remember a French
president ever resigning. What happens
when a French president resigns? They
have fixed what is it? Eightyear to uh
terms, 10-year terms. It's long.
>> It's f It used to be seven. Now, now
it's five.
>> So, the current
>> the current term is meant to uh end in
two years. So, uh I'm not sure what time
of the year it is. Um uh but what norm I
mean so the last time it happened uh I
believe was Charles de Gaul in uh in his
third time as president after the May
1968 student and union uprising that
almost uh caused a socialist revolution
in France. Um and at that and basically
what happens is that there's new
elections. Um, so and
>> and is it just to fill out the remainder
of the term
>> or does the new five-year term start?
>> No, I think Yeah. No, I think that's
just to that's I think Yeah, that's a
good question. I have to look that up. I
don't know the answer to that, John. I
think it's to finish the term, though.
Um, and then and then and then they can
run for reelection. There there's
currently a term limit. You can only
serve two terms. So I don't I think it's
analogous to ours in that like you could
I if Macron stepped down whoever the
person who wins could run theoretically
two more times and be elected. So uh it
it would work like that. But I I have to
look into that. Um and I don't know the
answer. Um but it's uh you know the
situation's very uh you know very
fraught. Um, you know, I McRone has been
just trying to play the same game over
and over and over and uh, you know, all
the French political observers from far
left to far right and everything in
between kind of agree that this just
can't go on. I mean, he basically just
keeps putting up these moderate centrist
corporist um, prime ministers who can't
form a government. I mean and the way
[clears throat] that the French
political uh alignment is now uh
everything has grabbed basically what
you have is you have a mushy small
minority party in the form of Macron's
party then over on the right you have a
unified right the the u under Marin Le
Pen
>> right
>> and Jordan Bardello her um her protege
then over on the left you have a an
alliance of convenience of left-wing
parties that all told add up to the
biggest plurality party. And so in the
last snap election that was held in
April of last year, that was called the
new popular front that's hearkening to
1936 and the old French popular front
which was a so again a front of uh the
socialist and communist and other
related parties. Um and they elected
back in 1936 famously France's first and
only Jewish president Leon Bloom um who
uh also instituted he was the FDR of
France. He instituted the French social
safety net as we know it today. So this
is very resonant. So we don't know if
the new popular front could reform. I
think they will. Um and so the the
question is when will Macron see
reality?
John, there is no world in which
Emmanuel Mcron finishes his term. No,
>> it is.
>> It's impossible. I mean, I think if he
lives to see if his if if he makes it to
to Christmas, he's lucky. Um I don't
think so.
>> Wow. Christmas is right around the
corner.
>> Yeah, I don't think it's, you know, I
mean, he's he's really on the ropes.
Look, it's I understand it's it's like
it's disgrace in the French system. It's
even more of a disgrace to step down as
president than it is for an American
president. It's bad. Like it's a blot
on, you know, on you in history. It's
just like what kind of [__] scandal
scarred loser are you? Um and you know,
I mean, you know, de Gaul had it coming.
He was just exhausted. He was so old by
then and he was so out of touch with the
youth and everything. They all he was
hated and reviled and basically he just
died shortly after resigning, right? Um,
Mcronone is a young man. Um, you know,
he's he has his whole life really ahead
of him. And so, you know, it's it's he's
got to be just like his head's spinning.
I don't think he can process it. I think
his little brain is little he's like the
little disc on your computer circling.
He can't he just can't believe this is
happening. He went from having total
control of the French Parliament to and
you know and the Elise palace and being
you know the dominant leader in Western
Europe to being like hated and reviled.
It's it's crazy. But you know they've
got to do something. Um
>> and uh you know also another thing
that's true is that the corporate
interests are not going to get their way
this time. um you know, sorry. Yeah, you
guys want like austerity and you want to
roll back the social safety net and you
want a low you want a a higher
retirement age and all that. You may get
it, but you're not getting it this time.
Um the the the far left and the far
right total probably account for about
70% or more of the vote. Um and and the
French people and not to mention cities
are going to burn. So um it's it's just
not going to happen. So, you know,
Mccronisma is finished. Now, this
becomes a struggle between the left and
the right. And um it would, if they're
smart, what they'll do is they'll put
together some kind of populist kind of
uh you know uh accommodation where
because there's a lot of stuff that they
can agree on. I mean, the right and like
unlike here in the United States, the
right in France believes in a social
safety net. Um, the right believes in
climate change and thinks that it's that
it's actually happening. The right cares
about the environment. So, they can do a
lot together. And they also put they
they also believe they both agree in
putting domestic interests first.
>> Ted, what do you what do you assess as
the chances for violence? The French,
one of the things I've always liked
about the French is that they're very
quick to go out into the streets. You
know, we saw the yellow vest protest. I
mean, look, going back to 68 and the
student protests of 68. Do you see that
happening again in the short term?
>> Um [sighs]
the prelim I mean I think the chances
for violence are better than 50/50. Um
the the question is how far will the
violence go? I mean there's already been
violence, right? I mean there's been
running street battles between the Siri
and uh and the and the protesters.
There's, you know, trash fires. There's
like there's been strikes. Um there's
been suppressed really violently. You
know, the French cops um you know, the
national police, they're goons. They're
mean as [__] Um and and they just tend
to to raise the temperature. So there
Yeah, I mean I think violence definitely
is going to happen. The question is how
far will it go and uh you know, how and
how much how far will the government be
willing to go to suppress it? It could.
I mean, honestly, I don't really see the
limit just yet. Um there's got to be
one, but I don't I I don't know. It's
the French are, you know, like you said.
Um Mustello uh Matzerati John is is
saying, "I will also help donate and
stay in touch through RT.
>> I have Sachs and McGovern on Speed
Dial." Um
Frog [laughter]
Enthusiast 235 says, "I think you
underestimate how much Mcron will do not
to resign." I always love these like
nicknames that people have on the
internet. I was never able to come up
with good ones.
It's like like I'm always
[laughter]
>> Ted Raw 1963, right?
>> Yeah. Like no, it's it's I'm a boring
person that way. Um yeah, they someone
once was making fun of me and calling me
Tokyo Rose and they called me Cobble Ted
back during the war of terrorists and so
I took it for myself. I thought it was
hilarious. But yeah. Um, hey John, do
you worry about Kimberly Gilfoil in
Greece? That's a question
>> wants to know.
>> Greek. Yes. Yes. Greeks are worried
about Kimberly Gilfoil. Yes. They're
being very nice about it. They're not
being too terribly public about it, but
they don't like her. They believe that
she's a lightweight. They don't care if
she was once an assistant US attorney.
Does not matter to anybody. Um, you
know, the the Greeks the Greeks are used
to
having um professional diplomats as
American ambassadors. Every once in a
while there's a political appointee,
>> but they tend to be Greek Americans,
wealthy Greek Americans who already have
close ties to the Greek government, and
so that's fine, too. Um, but this this
is something the Greeks are not happy
about. I will say she's probably smarter
than we generally give her credit for.
>> Um,
so I don't know.
>> She needs a better She needs a better
rhinoplasty expert though.
>> Yeah,
>> that was I mean, you know, the Dead
Kennedy's, one of my favorite bands, had
an album called Plastic Surgery
Disasters. I always think of that title
whenever I look at her.
>> Yeah, she needs uh the the doctors from
botched.
[laughter]
>> Yeah. I know. I mean, maybe maybe it's
like the $6 million man. We have the
technology. We can rebuild her.
[laughter]
>> Maybe. Um.
>> Okay. So, all right. So, is that enough?
That's is that So, so that's it for
France. Maybe. What do you want to talk?
What should we do now? Shut down.
>> Well, yeah, we should talk about the
shutdown, too. Donald Trump made a
statement yesterday that was just so
so typically Trump and so
silly. He said that, okay, he's willing
to talk about Obamacare subsidies, but
only after the government reopens.
That's the point of the shutdown,
>> right?
>> It's shut down because you can't agree
on Obamacare subsidies. So, what he's
saying is he's willing to talk about o
Obamacare subsidies if the Democrats
walk away from them,
>> right? Which is ridiculous.
>> Ridiculous.
>> I mean, here's the thing. I mean,
>> it's a waste of breath to even say it.
>> True. Now the thing is though he Donald
Trump even though the polls are running
against the Republicans on the shutdown.
Um the the thing is that the Republicans
I mean the Democrats I mean sorry the
Republicans do have one major thing
going for them which is that the
Democratic messaging has been [__] on
this. And so I mean all that all the
Democrats need to do is say look today's
October 7th. on October 15th, millions
of Americans are going to start getting
kicked off Medicaid because that's the
deadline for 2026 healthare. They miss
that. The subsidies aren't in place by
October 14th. Um, in a week, a week from
today, then the system's going to start
to collapse and by November 15th is
another round of deadlines for the
non-medicaid, for the people who are
like middle class and just need a
government subsidy. those people are
going to be kicked out of the system or
maybe not. They'll they'll they'll just
have to pay a [__] ton more. So, you
know, instead of paying, you know, 200 a
month, they might have to pay a thousand
a month or more. Um, you know, the the
some of the basic plans here in New York
City are $1,400 or $1,600 a month. And
and that's with like $10,000 deductibles
and stuff. Um,
>> yeah, mine's I pay 9.83 a month. It's
>> and I told you my doctor said to me when
I went to the doctor last time, he said,
"Why do you have this [__] insurance?"
>> Well, that's that's Obamacare a month.
Yep.
>> Yeah. Yeah. It's it's by county. It's
very very It's a shitty system. But the
only thing worse than a shitty system is
no system at all. And that's kind of
like what the Republicans want. So the
the Democrats haven't been messaging.
They haven't been running any ads on
social or on TV. Uh so there's, you
know, they're they're not getting their
message through. Nobody really knows
basically we just it's you know what
this is really about.
>> It's frustrating John because I think
the head I think the deadline's going to
lapse u the way things are going and
then the the thing is if millions of
people who are kicked off the health
care system are no longer in it by next
year it's not like Humpty Dumpty is
going to be put back together again by
next year. I mean not with this
president not with this Congress. So the
ACA will just crumble. The Democrats
can't go along with it. They just can't
because literally I think I mean John,
I've been thinking about this. I think
this is a grave crisis for the
Democratic party. I mean they're already
in deep trouble. If they let this go,
they will be blamed for the end of the
health care system. If they they can't
give those seven Senate votes to Donald
Trump. They can't.
>> So the government stays shut down. I
mean, obviously, Congress could pass
some kind of work around that says we're
changing all the deadlines. We're, you
know, but but that's more work. That's
going to be, you know, that's going to
require almost something that feels like
a grand bargain. Hard to imagine between
these two political parties at this
time. But the Democrats, I don't think
the Republicans know that the Democrats
can't go along with this. This is
something, you know, when you negotiate,
you have to know what the other side
needs and what they want. The Democrats
need this. They have to have it. I don't
know if the Republicans understand that.
>> Yeah, I think they don't.
>> Or if they care.
>> I think they don't. But I I agree with
you, U Ted, that Democratic messaging is
as bad as I've seen it be since the 1994
Republican contract with America.
I kept waiting in 1994 for the Democrats
to say something, to come up with some
proposal, some policy, and it was
nothing. And that's how it is again this
year. They don't stand for anything.
>> Tammy Landing says, "The Dems can
effectively complicate a wet dream."
>> Indeed.
>> I think we've got an I think we've got
an ad, Ted.
>> All right, we're ready for it, Robbie.
Whenever you're ready to put that up,
I'll I'll I'll I'll blast through it.
Um,
okay. So, yeah. So, I think this goes
on.
We should talk about Gaza.
>> Yeah, we should.
>> Um, so it's been it's been two years
since the October 7th attack. Okay,
we'll hold that there. Here's the ad.
Still haven't tried 1775 coffee? Now's
your shot. The 1775 starter kit just
dropped. Only 1,000 units. You're
getting the bolt dark roast that hits
hard, the smooth medium roast, and the
vitality mushroom coffee for clean
energy and laser focus. No crash. All
single origin, small batch, toxin-free
and mold-free. Plus, you're also getting
a gold spoon clip because freedom isn't
scooped with plastic. A frother strong
enough to stir up your coffee and your
mother-in-law's opinions. And a black
1775 tumbler. $170 worth of coffee and
gear. Yours for $99. This is for the
ones that who've been watching 1775 blow
up on Rumble. Wondering if it's actually
worth it? Spoiler, it is. Go to 1775
coffee.com/studio and grab your starter
kit before they're gone. Bold beans,
clean fuel, and a morning routine that
stands for something just like Rumble
does. Okay. So, so obviously we all know
what happened on October 7th, 2023. Not
going to re revisit all that. We all
know what's happened to Gaza. Um but
right now as we're talking um you know
it looks like uh Trump secretly behind
the scenes was really pissed off at BB
Netanyahu and has
>> he embarrassed Netanyahu embarrassed him
by bombing gutter. That was the breaking
point.
>> That was it. That did him in. That's why
he was like okay you're going to call
and apply to the cuttery uh apologize to
the cutteries and promise to never do
anything like that again. And
hilariously, Donald Trump has now
personally given a uh protection packed
to the cutteries like I will protect you
militarily in the event of an attack
presumably that would involve an maybe
against an attack by the IDF. I mean
that would that would be an attack is an
attack, right? That's the attack that
happens most recently and therefore most
likely to happen in the future. Um, and
so, you know, and then he when the uh
when Hamas cleverly dragged their feet
and said, you know, like, okay, we'll
give you back all the hostages, Donald
Trump said, peace is at hand. Peace in
our time. Neville Chamberlain, we're
done. We're good. Everyone come home.
You know, like victory parade,
>> Nobel Nobel Prize. And like, and that
and now Netanyahu is between a rock and
a hard place. He can't say no, but he
has to say no. So, he's going to scuttle
things. I agree with you that like he's
attacking Iran or something like it.
Most likely Iran is going to be his way
out or at least so he hopes. I don't
know if that'll work with Donald Trump
because someone around the table has to
have been have told Donald Trump this is
what BB's going to do. Um and so he
Trump's going to have seen it coming and
not like it. Um
>> yeah,
>> I think that the Hamas Hamas won the
war. Hamas uh carried out one of the
most brilliant um you know um raids in
mo in the modern history of warfare. I
mean they were outmatched militarily,
economically
uh in in certainly in terms of
diplomatically uh in every way and they
waged asymmetric warfare
um and they and and they've prevailed
and like you could say okay well you
know tens if not hundreds of thousands
of Gazins are dead as a as a result and
that's true.
>> Yes. But they're going to end up with
something that feels like a Palestinian
state. And I don't think it'll be a
demilitarized bound. I think it's going
to be the real [__] thing. And I
think it's going to be sooner rather
than later.
I think that's probably right. Something
is going to happen in favor of the
Palestinians.
Netanyahu has put Israel into an
untenable position when your only
choices are to continue fighting in an
unpopular war. And we talked yesterday
about about tripling in the number of
IDF uh soldiers who are committing
suicide.
Uh or
your second choice is to bomb Iran again
unprovoked again.
Those are not winning combinations.
>> No. And you don't have to love Iran to
put your foot down this time and say,
"Look, enough is enough. You can't just
bomb your way out of this, right? They
bombed Gaza. They bombed Lebanon. They
bombed Iran. They bombed Iran a second
time. They bombed Iran a third time.
They bombed Yemen and killed the prime
minister.
And it hasn't gotten them anything.
So, it's time to negotiate a
settlement." And I agree with you, Ted,
that anything the Palestinians get is
better what they have than what they
have now.
>> Yeah. And better, and I would argue
better than what they had before 2023.
Um,
>> they were they were living in in misery.
Uh,
>> well, they had what, two two hours of of
electricity a day, five hours of water,
or maybe I got it reversed.
>> Hyperinflation.
um you know, every uh staggeringly high
unemployment. Um the and and the you
know, the Israelis would sometimes let
workers out. Um you know, but then on a
drop of a hat, like if they had an itchy
ass, they would like they would close
the border. Um you know, no, I mean,
these are these are two I mean, I think
to me
all eyes are going to be turning to the
West Bank. That to me is the really
sticky wiki now. Um, you know, if if I'm
and of course there's the question, I
guess Hamas gets to keep Gaza and Fatah
gets to keep the whatever's left of the
West Bank.
>> Yeah.
>> But, you know, I mean, what do you do
about these 700,000 colonists in the
West Bank who have no legal basis to be
in, you know, on Palestinian land?
>> Yeah. Well, they've got to go, but I
mean, you know, you know the argument
like
>> they're not going to go.
>> Yeah. They're not going to go. It's like
the the Yeah, they're the facts on the
ground. These are children who were born
here and raised here. This is their
homes, too. Why can't the Palestinians
share? Why are they so chish?
>> Yeah. You know, that's why that's why
people are just now beginning to talk
about a three-state solution,
right? The the West Bank is independent
Palestine.
The Israelis get to keep Israel plus
whatever settlements they're able to
negotiate and
somebody
administers Gaza.
>> Well, that would solve one problem, but
it would create at least one more,
right? So, it would solve the issue of
the fact that you have two non-ontiguous
territories, right? Yes. Um there was
always conversations about how there
needs to be some kind of corridor like a
highway that's protected between the two
that goes through Israel. Um but that
you I mean you and I both know like from
history non-ontiguous territory causes
trouble. Um East Pakistan and Pakistan
and so on. Um
>> so um but it creates another problem. I
can see how Gaza can be viable. Gaza can
be a tourist attraction e, you know, not
necessarily Trump's vision in his AI
video, but it can be beautiful beaches,
stunning beaches, beautiful, beautiful
climate, great place to visit, good
food, every what's not to like? Um,
they've got oil as we've talked about.
So, you know, they can so that between
tourism and natural resources, Gaza can
make it.
>> The West Bank doesn't have anything,
right? I mean, it I don't think it's vi
economically viable. It would be like
lutu. It would be a locked landlocked,
cut off from the world, no natural
resources, desperately poor. I mean,
here I don't want to sound like some
Zionists, but some Zionists just have
suggested that that should go back to
Jordan. And I think maybe that's right.
>> Could be,
>> you know,
>> could be.
>> But that's a deal, I guess, that the
West Bank authorities could negotiate
with the Jordanians. Maybe they become
like a Kurdistan kind of autonomous
zone.
>> You know, they have autonomous status
with the way that Wizerstan does with
Pakistan.
>> You know, it's it's part of Jordan. They
pay taxes.
>> They the Jordanian army comes in when
there's a crisis, but not generally,
>> right?
Yeah. Half the population of Jordan is
Palestinian anyway.
>> Yeah.
>> So, that that could work.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I mean, yeah, it'll be
interesting to see how it all plays out.
John, do you think Donald Trump will be
the person who um who is able to
negotiate this three-state or two and a
half state solution?
>> No, I I honestly don't. Donald Trump is
definitely not a detail guy.
>> No.
>> You know, I've got this story that I've
told a number of times, Ted. Um a friend
of mine was at Camp David the in the
final week of the Clinton
administration. He was the senior
director at the National Security
Council for Middle Eastern Affairs and
talks between Israel and the
Palestinians were taking place under the
direction of Vice President Gore who was
very much a detail man as was Clinton.
And my buddy said that on the last day
they had this enormous map of Jerusalem
on the table and with a Sharpie they're
literally dividing Jerusalem block by
block. And when they finished Gore said,
"My God, we have peace."
And
Yaser Arafat said, "I can never sell
this to the Palestinian people." And he
walked out. Gore ran out after him and
he said, "Wait a minute. You can't just
walk out. If you don't like the deal,
then we can renegotiate whatever it is
that you don't like." And he said, "I
can never sell any deal to the
Palestinian people." And that was the
end of it. And then Clinton said in his
memoir, his first memoir, that he wished
he had
spent that week not trying to negotiate
peace between the Palestinians and the
Israelis, but instead trying to open
diplomatic relations with the North
Koreans. You may remember, maybe you
don't, but I do, um, Maline Albbright,
the Secretary of State at the time, was
not at those Israeli Arab-Israeli talks
because she was in Pyongyang.
convince the North Koreans to open
diplomatic relations. So instead of, you
know, walking away from one to to
strengthen the other and then come out
with a victory,
>> we ended up with two failures.
>> That sucks.
>> So my point is
Gore and Clinton were detail guys. Trump
is absolutely positively not a detail
guy. So if the detail guys couldn't work
out the details, then the guy who just
says make peace or else he's not gonna
make
>> I mean it's been mentioned, right? But
like you know Trump is a uh you know I
think it comes from Trump's business
background. When you do a real estate
deal or a big financial transaction, you
have a deal sheet with the basic points
that's usually a single piece of paper
and has like a set of bullet points that
basically says you know you know Kuryaku
Corp is is uh you know selling 40% to R
Corp and you know we're going to have an
exchange of this many shares and this
office will belong to you and that
office belong to me but it's just very
basic. it might just be a few hundred
words and then all the details are are
hashed out by the lawyers uh and then
you know ultimately codified and sign
and that's what he's used to. He's not
used to, you know, like a Paris
Versailles 1919 kind of, you know,
conference where you're sitting over
pouring over a a map of Kurdistan trying
to uh figure out what part of it goes to
Turkey and what part of it ends up in
Iraq and where Iraq should be and why
and like the
>> somebody call the British. [laughter]
>> Yeah, of course.
>> British cgraphers have never caused any
problems, right? Um, so yeah. No, I I I
see that, but I mean, but a but a weird
part here is we are somehow closer to
something than we've ever been. Is that
due to Donald Trump or is that due to
Hamas or is that due to both?
>> Yeah, I think it's due to Hamas and I
think it's due also in part
to the
historic overreaction.
of uh Benjamin Netanyahu.
>> Well, that was his big mistake, right? I
mean, imagine I mean, first of all, I
just want to hand it to Hamas
strategically, right? I mean, they
literally they played this long game
probably for at least 5 to 10 years.
They they created the, you know, the
Gaza subway, right? They created this
massive struct infrastructure of tunnels
so that they to prepare for this future
when there would be another Israeli
onslaught even bigger than anything
they'd ever seen before. And then they
launched the raid and they pro to
provoke this reaction which they wanted
a big blockbuster reaction. The most the
the worst from a from the Palestinian
perspective, the worst thing could have
happened is would have been for the
Israelis to treat this like a like a
like a crime to ask the to ask Hamas to
to arrest the perpetrators, cloal the
border, ask Hamas to extradite anyone
who's guilty. Uh maybe just do a
pinpoint like commando raid into into
Gaza.
>> That would have absolutely like killed
them. they would have been in cutter
like [__] they didn't fall for our trap.
Um
>> yes yes I agree completely
>> but you but I think they're all like
toasting each other like yeah like
everything came up Hamas you know like
that like like in the Simpsons
everything's coming up Milhouse. Um,
it's [laughter] like I love that
>> and it's and it's like this is not by
the way to praise I'm you know I have
nothing in common with Hamas or their
ideology or their religion at all. Uh I
would not like to live under their rule.
I'm just saying like good job tactically
though really. Um
>> very good job tactically.
>> So let's see. Um
oh yeah so Philip Blair 9511 says the
Germans were emptied out of Coninsburg.
families who'd lived there for
centuries. That's true. I mean,
certainly there's been mass
displacements, displacements of people
many times. Look, there were Israeli
settled settlers in Gaza and they were
forced to to they were kicked out by the
IDF before
>> and and Sinai.
>> Yeah. A lot of them. Yeah.
>> A lot. Whole towns.
>> And just recently in Norno Carabach,
right, the um the uh the Azeris kicked
out the Armenians, ethnic Armenians. So
I mean yeah you can have mass
displacements of people and you know the
these are people who shouldn't be there.
So uh when we're talking about the West
Bank settlers and the numbers are just
so crazy. I mean
>> agreed
>> they possess 60% of the of the West Bank
in terms of the land. So
>> it's crazy.
>> I mean it's like what the hell. Um
>> little breaking thing if I could. Oh. Oh
no. You have breaking news.
>> Little breaking news. Uh Robbie just put
it up. New York Times is reporting that
gold is now at $4,000 an ounce amid uh
turmoil and uh you know nervousness and
anxiety in the mark in the securities
markets.
>> Yeah. 4,000 is one of those
psychological thresholds that's never
been met before. So that's at a record.
Silver has moved even more strongly into
record territory. And now people are
predicting uh that Bitcoin will soon
follow.
Well, at least gold's got inherent
value, unlike Bitcoin. The thing is, you
know, I'm I'm old enough to remember
when gold had a fixed rate of $35 an
ounce in 1973.
>> Yep.
>> Man, man, I I wish I'd say I'd put I'd
used my paper route money to buy gold.
>> Yeah. I wish I had like
>> I remember those days.
>> Yeah. $35.
>> Nixon changed it for everybody.
>> Yeah, he did. Yeah, he Yeah, I mean I I
have to I do understand the gold bug
thing completely. I mean there's
something very like it, you know, primal
about like like I want to be like a
bridge troll. I want gold. It's so
beautiful. But it is
>> it is never tarnishes.
>> I want those uh I I lust for those $20
gold pieces. [laughter]
I used to collect coins avidly. Now it's
just I don't I don't do that anymore. I
like paper currency better.
>> It's it's really affordable
>> and it's and it's cool. Yeah. The
graphics and everything.
>> I always uh I always keep my euros when
I come home from a trip to Europe.
Always
>> I miss the French Franks
>> when I Oh, do you still have Franks?
>> Yeah. Yeah. With the with the you know
with like Mullier and stuff like that.
So beautiful. I have a lot of old
dramas. I anytime I encounter an old
Dramma that's made out of silver like
pre-1964.
>> I I buy it and just toss it in a bag of
you know hundreds of other dramas.
[laughter]
>> Well, I mean it says something when you
know like I tried I explained that to my
kid like you know so you understand like
if you want to know what this what
happened to this country dimes and
quarters were 90% silver until 1965.
[laughter]
I mean that's tells you a lot about a
country. [snorts] You know if you go
back and look at um you know World War
II currency like Vichi coins, they were
aluminum and they had a hole punched in
the middle because they couldn't even
afford the the you know the aluminum or
the tin that they used to make them.
>> Yeah. How embarrassing.
>> It is embarrassing. Well, you know,
John, they don't even you know like when
they redesigned, you know, the $20 bill
to to its current iteration. I don't
know if you read this, but you know,
it's obviously it's an incredibly ugly
bill. It's like it's just it's it's it's
uh it's off prop the poor proportions
are all off wildly and it just looks
like someone who you know was dropped on
their head at birth like designed it,
right? And then they were interviewed, I
think it was in the New York Times, they
inter they called the mint and they said
the mint said confided that they had not
hired a graphic designer to to do this
for literally the the US $20 bill is the
most widely circulated bill in the
world, right? It's the standard like
people keep 20s and hundreds like you
know all over the world um as their
savings. And like no graphic designer
had anything to do with they said their
only concern was anti- was
anti-counterfeiting measures. They did
not care what it looked like.
>> And it's like this is a, you know, it's
like a step forward, you know.
Meanwhile, it's sort of like what
happened. I don't know if you remember
this incident like with postage stamps,
but about I think 10 years ago, one of
the forever stamps with the Statue of
Liberty head on it, it turned out that
it was a a a photo of the Statue of
Liberty on top of the New York New York
casino in Las Vegas.
um it was not the actual. And so it
turned out that the post office had paid
$8 to a um to a uh uh um to a company
that has stock photography for the
rights to this photo and nobody bothered
to check whether it was the real thing
or not. So they literally put out a
stamp that that had the wrong Statue of
Liberty on it. And back in the day, if
there was a [__] like that, the postal
service would have shredded recalled the
run and shredded them all. and they
would have become highly desirable. Like
they're like, "Ah, keep printing them,
whatever." Meanwhile, like back in like
the 1930s, if you if you engrave
>> if you engrave just like a little stamp
that was like a one a two cent stamp
that was like had a picture of like
Andrew Jackson on it or something. You
those guys literally got $100,000 to
engrave a stamp like that
>> in the depression. in the depression.
>> Um Tariq, thank thanks for the donation.
Bosnia, he says, is the real ideal
solution for the country is divided up
to accommodate three ethnic groups.
Dayton peaceful but not ideal.
>> Yeah, we've talked about that. Well,
we've touched on it a couple of times.
Um, Bosnia, I think, would have to be
the model because if you look at a map
of Bosnia, it's got all these little
islands of, you know, of not Bosnia,
whether it's Republica, Serpska, I
always hated that name,
>> Republic.
>> Um, or whatever else, whatever else they
were able to negotiate that is Serb. Um,
it has worked against all odds and maybe
that's the model that that the world
needs to be thinking about.
[snorts]
>> Could could work. Um,
>> hey, real real quick, Ted.
>> Yeah,
>> we only have about 11 minutes left, so I
wanted to raise this whole Gain Maxwell
thing,
>> please.
>> You know, Trump said something yesterday
that was very, very disturbing. Uh,
somebody asked him if he was going to
pardon Galain Maxwell and he said
disingenuously
um he hadn't thought about it. Oh, I
haven't heard that name in a long time.
He said, [laughter]
>> "God, the lying
like and he knows I mean he must know
that nobody believes him." But anyway,
um and then he said, "Oh, a lot of
people ask me for pardons." Uh, and then
the reporter followed up by shouting,
"Uh, are you considering pardoning her?"
And he said, "Uh, well, I haven't heard
that name in a long time. I'm going to
have to take a look at it."
This is a this is a convicted child
molester and sex trafficker. Child sex
trafficker.
Let's say he doesn't even pardon her.
Let's say he commutes her sentence,
which is just as good,
>> right? Pretty much. What does that do to
Donald Trump among Republicans? [snorts]
Because remember, it's the Republicans
who think that the government is made up
of child molesters and and sex
traffickers,
>> right? And there's this secret cabal
that, you know, eats the hearts of
children or whatever.
>> Um, what does that do
to Trump and his coalition? Robbie, I
think Robbie and I agree. Robbie just
texted, "Nothing will destroy Trump's
coalition faster than him barding her."
I agree.
I think he's really playing with fire
here and maybe he just doesn't even
realize it.
>> I I think he realizes it and that's why
he's dragging his feet. He's rolling
Hamas style on this. Um, you know, he
he's definitely he knows it's going to
fracture his coalition. He knows it's
really it's fraught. But let let me flip
this on the other let's look at this
Rubik's cube from the other side. What
happens if he doesn't pardon her? What's
the downside for him or commuter
sentence?
>> The the downside
is that somebody out there, and I'm just
making this up, somebody out there has
documentary evidence
that he committed a crime. Let's even
assume that the statute of limitations
has expired.
>> There's documentary evidence that he was
somehow involved with with Jeffrey
Epstein and it's released. That's the
only thing I can think of.
>> Well, she's been transferred to that
minimum security.
>> Minimum security despite the fact that
if you have been convicted of a sex
crime, you are not eligible to be sent
to minimum security.
>> So why why did that happen?
>> That was a personal favor. First of all,
only the attorney general can order
that, right? Or the attorney general on
behalf of the president, but the
attorney general makes that decision.
So, I mean, the obvious answer is there
has to be some sort of quid proquo.
>> It feels like there's some Look, there's
some kind of there's something hanging
over Donald Trump. We don't know what it
is. We can guess, but it I mean, he
could just say I mean, if there wasn't,
why wouldn't he just say, "Fuck her.
Lock her, you know, she's locked up.
Throw away the key and see you. See you
in 20 years. Bye."
>> Yeah.
>> Um,
>> thank you. Thank you, Real Real, for
those kind comments. Appreciate
>> I wanted to you, you know, I did want to
ask you, John, I was very curious what
you'd think about this. So, I read um in
in with great interest and some and
considerable detail her appeal to the US
Supreme Court.
>> Yes. Which was denied yesterday, day
before,
>> which was denied. Frankly, I thought she
was wronged. I think I think she made a
good point. I mean, she was arguing. So,
basically back in 2008 when Jeffrey
Epstein was uh you know basically cut a
deal with prosecutors down in Florida
for sex crimes uh and they they agreed
not to prosecute him or any of his
associates who were involved. That would
include her. Um she claims that she
should have therefore been covered on
these charges in New York. These are all
federal charges. her argue her lawyer's
argument was if you make a deal if I Ted
R make a deal with federal prosecutors
here in New York City. Uh, and I say
it's and like I'm, you know, I'm a I'm
I'm free to go. You know, you can't
critic, you can't you can't prosecute me
for this that crime that pro federal
prosecutors in Oregon shouldn't be able
to touch me either because it's one
country. It's the United States. It's
the federal authority is over the entire
country. And the or the Oregon
prosecutors can't say, "Well, we're the
we're the Oregon district." Like, no.
Like, I made a deal. You guys made a
deal and you said I could walk. I think
she's right.
>> She may be. Well, she may be
>> like philosophically, but this said no.
>> Yeah. So, this is I mean to me this was
a political decision on the on the part
of the US Supreme Court. I think they
were they knew and that's why they
didn't issue a formal opinion.
>> Yeah.
>> It's just sort of like
>> it's sort of just it's just sort of like
just know.
It's like you and I have talked about
how we had certain decisions in our
cases that basically came down to if
your name is John Kuryaku or Ted Bra,
this law does not apply to you.
>> So if if your name is Gizlain Maxwell,
this law does not apply to you. I don't
know. It's I mean all every time
something like this happens, John, it
always makes me wonder why do people
make deals what with the feds? Why do
they trust them not to like reneg?
I mean, look at look at you. They
reneged with you. They said you were
going to a to a camp. They said you were
going to club fed. Then you arrive and
they're like, "Fuck you. You're going to
the real clink." I mean, it everybody
hears about these stories. It's like,
why on earth? It's like, if I were ever
arrested, I'd be like, I don't believe a
word you say. You guys are liars.
>> That's right. That's right. Um, I can
tell you why people take a deal and and
it's it's 98% of federal criminal cases
end in a plea bargain. Um, and it's
because of uh something called uh
federal sentencing enhancements.
So, if you turn down a deal and go to
trial and are found guilty,
>> they add time
>> to your sentence for what they call
failure to accept responsibility.
>> Ridiculous.
>> Yeah.
>> Isn't that Isn't that unconstitutional?
Because it's punishing you for your
decision to def to avail yourself of
your of your constitutional right to to
defend yourself.
>> That's right. Yes, you're exactly right.
Um, I assume that's been adjudicated.
Um, unfortunately. Hey, so Robbie's
bringing up another interesting point.
He said, "We're forgetting about uh
Thomas Massiey's bill forcing the
release of the Epstein files." Massie
announced on social a day or two ago
that he has the 218 votes necessary to
to force the release and that this the
real reason that the Republicans are
letting the government stay shut down is
because that way the House isn't
reconvened and and that that's not going
to come up for a vote.
Wow. He's got the 218. So, what we're
talking about here is his what's called
his discharge petition.
>> These things only come once a decade
>> when the when the House leadership has a
bill bottled up in committee or
subcommittee
and you want it to go to the floor
>> um of the House for a vote. You have to
file a discharge petition which
discharges it from the committee.
Usually the rules committee. the rules
committee decides what goes to a vote
and what doesn't. But then it's
complicated. It used to be that the
rules committee was the most powerful
committee in the in the House and now
it's the speaker that decides what the
rules committee releases. So, but
anyway,
thanks to N. Gingrich. Anyway, um if
Massie has 218 votes,
that's all Democrats
and five Republicans.
And that means the vote will be likely
218 to two I I guess it's 16 now because
there's still a vacancy
and all of those Jeffrey Epstein
documents will be made public.
>> You know Messi is one of my favorite
members of Congress. This guy doesn't
give a [__] if he gets reelected or not.
>> That's great.
>> It's great. It's It's got to be
liberating.
>> Oh, totally.
only in getting the truth out there.
>> John, it's time to wrap things up, but
before we do, let's bring in Robbie for
one last uh reminder and push for people
who are just joining us. Hey, Robbie, we
see your shoulder. It's a beautiful
shoulder. I love your shoulder.
>> It's the best shoulder. Yeah. Sorry, I
was getting tmi ready to go. Speaking of
tmi, uh we are building a network. So,
if you're here on Rumble, just stay
tuned. We're going to be rating the tmi
show where you get to see more Ted R,
less uh John Keryaku, but you do get to
see the beautiful Manila Chan. So, it's,
you know, there's a win. There's a win
and a loss. There's there's a little
toss up there. We'll just call it what
it is. But the biggest reason why I
wanted to just come back on is that over
on YouTube, we currently have 225 people
watching us on YouTube. Uh, for those of
you who tuned in late, uh, YouTube has
demonetized, deprogrammed. John and Ted
get nothing from YouTube anymore.
>> Dangerous content.
>> We are, we are trying to appeal it. Uh,
but I mean, let's just be honest.
YouTube is big because it's supported by
the people who silenced John and Ted in
the past.
So I am I am asking you if you want this
show to continue please follow them on
Rumble. They are fully monetized on
Rumble. They are Rumble partners. You
can donate there. You become channel
subscribers for five bucks a month. See
>> we have started to get money. We have
started to see money from Rumble.
>> They have. But we need y'all's help
because for every one person that's over
that's watching on Rumble, there's two
or three of you that are watching on
YouTube.
We need y'all's help.
I am working for these guys for free
because I refuse to take a dime from
them while they cannot pay their bills.
And so if I'm able to do that, the least
you can do is go over it and watch
>> here. Here. Thank you very much, Robbie
West.
>> That's all I've got to say. And uh just
one quick thing just about Epste will go
away. If Trump wants to destroy the
Republican party, all he has to do is
release uh Maxwell. That will end the
Republican coalition. That will destroy
the Republican party. I promise you,
it's a creature from the right. And on
that, I got to go to TMI.
>> Okay. And so do I. We'll be back
tomorrow here with uh with Dro with Ted
Ren, John Kuryaku at 9:00 a.m. Eastern
time. John, watch out for the
tarantulas, the snakes, and the
mosquitoes, and the hurricanes.
>> But otherwise, it's paradise. Yeah.
>> Yeah. It's wonderful. Wonderful.
>> Bye. Bye. Bye.